{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956421906","data":{"timestamp":" 946956421906"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" e15b0921-d038-491e-9b49-5192afb85018"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_H-D-P"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956425492","data":{"timestamp":" 946956425492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" e15b0921-d038-491e-9b49-5192afb85018"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_E-V-P"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956429028","data":{"timestamp":" 946956429028"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" e15b0921-d038-491e-9b49-5192afb85018"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_I-P-R"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956432743","data":{"timestamp":" 946956432743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" e15b0921-d038-491e-9b49-5192afb85018"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-M-Z"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956436296","data":{"timestamp":" 946956436296"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" e15b0921-d038-491e-9b49-5192afb85018"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_U-P-H"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956439763","data":{"timestamp":" 946956439763"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" e15b0921-d038-491e-9b49-5192afb85018"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-J-CH"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956443759","data":{"timestamp":" 946956443759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" e15b0921-d038-491e-9b49-5192afb85018"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-E-S"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956447288","data":{"timestamp":" 946956447288"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" e15b0921-d038-491e-9b49-5192afb85018"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-D-V"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956451250","data":{"timestamp":" 946956451250"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" e15b0921-d038-491e-9b49-5192afb85018"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_E-P-M"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956454521","data":{"timestamp":" 946956454521"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" e15b0921-d038-491e-9b49-5192afb85018"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-T"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956460310","data":{"timestamp":" 946956460309"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" e15b0921-d038-491e-9b49-5192afb85018"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-T"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956477479","data":{"timestamp":" 946956477479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" e15b0921-d038-491e-9b49-5192afb85018"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-T"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956495855","data":{"timestamp":" 946956495854"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" e15b0921-d038-491e-9b49-5192afb85018"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-T"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956512340","data":{"timestamp":" 946956512339"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" f06076ab-57e2-4b49-b941-83caa9ae03ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956555205","data":{"timestamp":" 946956555204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" f06076ab-57e2-4b49-b941-83caa9ae03ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956555301","data":{"timestamp":" 946956555301"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" f06076ab-57e2-4b49-b941-83caa9ae03ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956575729","data":{"timestamp":" 946956575729"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" f06076ab-57e2-4b49-b941-83caa9ae03ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956596229","data":{"timestamp":" 946956596228"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 8878a92e-a66b-4330-907c-d0a7b248bfca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-Y-P"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956599858","data":{"timestamp":" 946956599858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 8878a92e-a66b-4330-907c-d0a7b248bfca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_S-V-P"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956603328","data":{"timestamp":" 946956603328"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 8878a92e-a66b-4330-907c-d0a7b248bfca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_M-S-P"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956608134","data":{"timestamp":" 946956608134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 8878a92e-a66b-4330-907c-d0a7b248bfca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_M-E-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956611688","data":{"timestamp":" 946956611688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 8878a92e-a66b-4330-907c-d0a7b248bfca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_N-E-P"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956616708","data":{"timestamp":" 946956616708"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 8878a92e-a66b-4330-907c-d0a7b248bfca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-N-M"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956628325","data":{"timestamp":" 946956628324"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 8878a92e-a66b-4330-907c-d0a7b248bfca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_L-P-W"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956632705","data":{"timestamp":" 946956632705"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 8878a92e-a66b-4330-907c-d0a7b248bfca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_D-P-Y"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956636474","data":{"timestamp":" 946956636474"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 8878a92e-a66b-4330-907c-d0a7b248bfca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_Y-T-P"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956639883","data":{"timestamp":" 946956639882"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 8878a92e-a66b-4330-907c-d0a7b248bfca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_K-Y-P"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956645662","data":{"timestamp":" 946956645662"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 8878a92e-a66b-4330-907c-d0a7b248bfca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_P_K-Y-P"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956657974","data":{"timestamp":" 946956657974"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" bf0813d2-2ef5-40bf-b70d-6305a521315a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_L-P-W"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956661494","data":{"timestamp":" 946956661494"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" bf0813d2-2ef5-40bf-b70d-6305a521315a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_K-Y-P"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956666086","data":{"timestamp":" 946956666086"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" bf0813d2-2ef5-40bf-b70d-6305a521315a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-N-M"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956669496","data":{"timestamp":" 946956669495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" bf0813d2-2ef5-40bf-b70d-6305a521315a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_Y-T-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956672939","data":{"timestamp":" 946956672939"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" bf0813d2-2ef5-40bf-b70d-6305a521315a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_D-P-Y"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956676636","data":{"timestamp":" 946956676636"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" bf0813d2-2ef5-40bf-b70d-6305a521315a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-Y-P"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956680836","data":{"timestamp":" 946956680836"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" bf0813d2-2ef5-40bf-b70d-6305a521315a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_M-S-P"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956684825","data":{"timestamp":" 946956684825"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" bf0813d2-2ef5-40bf-b70d-6305a521315a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_M-E-P"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956689520","data":{"timestamp":" 946956689520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" bf0813d2-2ef5-40bf-b70d-6305a521315a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_S-V-P"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956694950","data":{"timestamp":" 946956694949"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" bf0813d2-2ef5-40bf-b70d-6305a521315a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_N-E-P"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956700726","data":{"timestamp":" 946956700724"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" bf0813d2-2ef5-40bf-b70d-6305a521315a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_P_N-E-P"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956749994","data":{"timestamp":" 946956749993"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 50c01d8d-e238-4c40-a697-552476a10f4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Y_P_CH"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956756644","data":{"timestamp":" 946956756644"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 50c01d8d-e238-4c40-a697-552476a10f4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_J_U_P"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956763326","data":{"timestamp":" 946956763326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 50c01d8d-e238-4c40-a697-552476a10f4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_M_P_L"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956769978","data":{"timestamp":" 946956769977"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 50c01d8d-e238-4c40-a697-552476a10f4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_S_P_J"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956776635","data":{"timestamp":" 946956776634"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 50c01d8d-e238-4c40-a697-552476a10f4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_K_P_T"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956783257","data":{"timestamp":" 946956783256"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 50c01d8d-e238-4c40-a697-552476a10f4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_R_G_P"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956789909","data":{"timestamp":" 946956789908"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 50c01d8d-e238-4c40-a697-552476a10f4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Y_U_P"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956796570","data":{"timestamp":" 946956796569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 50c01d8d-e238-4c40-a697-552476a10f4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_V_J_P"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956803191","data":{"timestamp":" 946956803191"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 50c01d8d-e238-4c40-a697-552476a10f4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_J_P"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956809821","data":{"timestamp":" 946956809821"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 50c01d8d-e238-4c40-a697-552476a10f4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_P_R_S"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956821927","data":{"timestamp":" 946956821926"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 50c01d8d-e238-4c40-a697-552476a10f4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_P_R_S"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956855671","data":{"timestamp":" 946956855670"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956856725","data":{"timestamp":" 946956856725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956859942","data":{"timestamp":" 946956859941"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956861008","data":{"timestamp":" 946956861008"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956864602","data":{"timestamp":" 946956864601"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956865658","data":{"timestamp":" 946956865657"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956868278","data":{"timestamp":" 946956868278"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956869348","data":{"timestamp":" 946956869347"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956873633","data":{"timestamp":" 946956873632"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956874697","data":{"timestamp":" 946956874696"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956882220","data":{"timestamp":" 946956882219"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956883295","data":{"timestamp":" 946956883294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956886580","data":{"timestamp":" 946956886580"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956887645","data":{"timestamp":" 946956887644"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956895418","data":{"timestamp":" 946956895418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956896458","data":{"timestamp":" 946956896457"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956908049","data":{"timestamp":" 946956908048"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956909125","data":{"timestamp":" 946956909125"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956913119","data":{"timestamp":" 946956913119"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956914184","data":{"timestamp":" 946956914184"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956917356","data":{"timestamp":" 946956917355"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956918415","data":{"timestamp":" 946956918414"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956928295","data":{"timestamp":" 946956928295"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956929349","data":{"timestamp":" 946956929349"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956933308","data":{"timestamp":" 946956933307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956934363","data":{"timestamp":" 946956934362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956937847","data":{"timestamp":" 946956937846"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956938925","data":{"timestamp":" 946956938925"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956941599","data":{"timestamp":" 946956941598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956942663","data":{"timestamp":" 946956942663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956948012","data":{"timestamp":" 946956948012"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956949075","data":{"timestamp":" 946956949074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956954060","data":{"timestamp":" 946956954060"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956955108","data":{"timestamp":" 946956955107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956958338","data":{"timestamp":" 946956958337"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956959379","data":{"timestamp":" 946956959379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956963528","data":{"timestamp":" 946956963527"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956964585","data":{"timestamp":" 946956964584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956968118","data":{"timestamp":" 946956968117"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956969175","data":{"timestamp":" 946956969174"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956971724","data":{"timestamp":" 946956971723"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956972788","data":{"timestamp":" 946956972787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956976471","data":{"timestamp":" 946956976471"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956977515","data":{"timestamp":" 946956977514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956981249","data":{"timestamp":" 946956981248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956982324","data":{"timestamp":" 946956982323"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956986362","data":{"timestamp":" 946956986362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956987411","data":{"timestamp":" 946956987410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956990880","data":{"timestamp":" 946956990878"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946956991001","data":{"timestamp":" 946956991001"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 12e1dd05-2388-4933-ba16-2680ebd24bce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957020853","data":{"timestamp":" 946957020853"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 4c32c3af-fb9a-4711-b9de-68f992d4019c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957024790","data":{"timestamp":" 946957024790"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 4c32c3af-fb9a-4711-b9de-68f992d4019c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957029604","data":{"timestamp":" 946957029604"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 4c32c3af-fb9a-4711-b9de-68f992d4019c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957033899","data":{"timestamp":" 946957033899"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 4c32c3af-fb9a-4711-b9de-68f992d4019c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957037964","data":{"timestamp":" 946957037964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 4c32c3af-fb9a-4711-b9de-68f992d4019c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957041833","data":{"timestamp":" 946957041833"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 4c32c3af-fb9a-4711-b9de-68f992d4019c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957048718","data":{"timestamp":" 946957048718"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 4c32c3af-fb9a-4711-b9de-68f992d4019c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-H-A"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957052928","data":{"timestamp":" 946957052928"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 4c32c3af-fb9a-4711-b9de-68f992d4019c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957056593","data":{"timestamp":" 946957056593"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 4c32c3af-fb9a-4711-b9de-68f992d4019c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_N-I-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957059950","data":{"timestamp":" 946957059950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 4c32c3af-fb9a-4711-b9de-68f992d4019c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_B-J-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957064041","data":{"timestamp":" 946957064041"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 4c32c3af-fb9a-4711-b9de-68f992d4019c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_CH-K-D"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957071107","data":{"timestamp":" 946957071107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 4c32c3af-fb9a-4711-b9de-68f992d4019c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957075241","data":{"timestamp":" 946957075241"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 4c32c3af-fb9a-4711-b9de-68f992d4019c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957080024","data":{"timestamp":" 946957080023"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 4c32c3af-fb9a-4711-b9de-68f992d4019c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-I"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957084470","data":{"timestamp":" 946957084470"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 4c32c3af-fb9a-4711-b9de-68f992d4019c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_R-O-E"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957087982","data":{"timestamp":" 946957087982"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 4c32c3af-fb9a-4711-b9de-68f992d4019c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-W"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957091765","data":{"timestamp":" 946957091765"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 4c32c3af-fb9a-4711-b9de-68f992d4019c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-E-S"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957095516","data":{"timestamp":" 946957095515"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 4c32c3af-fb9a-4711-b9de-68f992d4019c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-L-S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957099708","data":{"timestamp":" 946957099708"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 4c32c3af-fb9a-4711-b9de-68f992d4019c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-Z-T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957103612","data":{"timestamp":" 946957103612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 4c32c3af-fb9a-4711-b9de-68f992d4019c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-CH-N"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957107797","data":{"timestamp":" 946957107797"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 4c32c3af-fb9a-4711-b9de-68f992d4019c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-A-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957112266","data":{"timestamp":" 946957112266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 4c32c3af-fb9a-4711-b9de-68f992d4019c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-U"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957115911","data":{"timestamp":" 946957115911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 4c32c3af-fb9a-4711-b9de-68f992d4019c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_F-Z-Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957119755","data":{"timestamp":" 946957119755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 4c32c3af-fb9a-4711-b9de-68f992d4019c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957125542","data":{"timestamp":" 946957125540"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 4c32c3af-fb9a-4711-b9de-68f992d4019c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957157240","data":{"timestamp":" 946957157240"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957159353","data":{"timestamp":" 946957159353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957161527","data":{"timestamp":" 946957161527"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957164744","data":{"timestamp":" 946957164743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957167028","data":{"timestamp":" 946957167027"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957169302","data":{"timestamp":" 946957169301"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957172197","data":{"timestamp":" 946957172196"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957174401","data":{"timestamp":" 946957174400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957176595","data":{"timestamp":" 946957176595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957179873","data":{"timestamp":" 946957179872"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957182003","data":{"timestamp":" 946957182003"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957184135","data":{"timestamp":" 946957184134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957187156","data":{"timestamp":" 946957187155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957189418","data":{"timestamp":" 946957189417"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957191647","data":{"timestamp":" 946957191646"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957194624","data":{"timestamp":" 946957194624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957196943","data":{"timestamp":" 946957196943"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957199335","data":{"timestamp":" 946957199334"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957202409","data":{"timestamp":" 946957202408"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957204554","data":{"timestamp":" 946957204553"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957206734","data":{"timestamp":" 946957206733"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957209902","data":{"timestamp":" 946957209902"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957212076","data":{"timestamp":" 946957212075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957214270","data":{"timestamp":" 946957214269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957217470","data":{"timestamp":" 946957217469"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957219872","data":{"timestamp":" 946957219871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957222262","data":{"timestamp":" 946957222261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957225389","data":{"timestamp":" 946957225388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957227651","data":{"timestamp":" 946957227650"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957229956","data":{"timestamp":" 946957229956"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957232973","data":{"timestamp":" 946957232973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957235189","data":{"timestamp":" 946957235188"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957237395","data":{"timestamp":" 946957237394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957240398","data":{"timestamp":" 946957240397"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957242735","data":{"timestamp":" 946957242734"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957245112","data":{"timestamp":" 946957245111"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957248246","data":{"timestamp":" 946957248245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957250667","data":{"timestamp":" 946957250666"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957253044","data":{"timestamp":" 946957253043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957255986","data":{"timestamp":" 946957255985"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957258295","data":{"timestamp":" 946957258294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957260578","data":{"timestamp":" 946957260578"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957263849","data":{"timestamp":" 946957263848"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957266146","data":{"timestamp":" 946957266146"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957268424","data":{"timestamp":" 946957268423"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957271835","data":{"timestamp":" 946957271834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957274251","data":{"timestamp":" 946957274251"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957276712","data":{"timestamp":" 946957276712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957279490","data":{"timestamp":" 946957279490"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957281605","data":{"timestamp":" 946957281605"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957283720","data":{"timestamp":" 946957283720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957287170","data":{"timestamp":" 946957287169"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957289482","data":{"timestamp":" 946957289481"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957291827","data":{"timestamp":" 946957291826"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957294976","data":{"timestamp":" 946957294975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957297263","data":{"timestamp":" 946957297262"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957299530","data":{"timestamp":" 946957299530"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957302585","data":{"timestamp":" 946957302584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957304743","data":{"timestamp":" 946957304743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957306880","data":{"timestamp":" 946957306879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957310060","data":{"timestamp":" 946957310059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957312315","data":{"timestamp":" 946957312314"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957314562","data":{"timestamp":" 946957314562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957317801","data":{"timestamp":" 946957317801"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957320029","data":{"timestamp":" 946957320029"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957322256","data":{"timestamp":" 946957322256"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957325513","data":{"timestamp":" 946957325512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957327848","data":{"timestamp":" 946957327848"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957330207","data":{"timestamp":" 946957330206"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957333343","data":{"timestamp":" 946957333342"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957335660","data":{"timestamp":" 946957335660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957337939","data":{"timestamp":" 946957337938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957341344","data":{"timestamp":" 946957341343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957341485","data":{"timestamp":" 946957341485"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" ac48e615-25a1-41e8-a306-dc1421e4a754"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957377726","data":{"timestamp":" 946957377725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957378108","data":{"timestamp":" 946957378107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957378602","data":{"timestamp":" 946957378601"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957378953","data":{"timestamp":" 946957378952"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957379368","data":{"timestamp":" 946957379367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957379848","data":{"timestamp":" 946957379847"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957380082","data":{"timestamp":" 946957380081"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957383331","data":{"timestamp":" 946957383330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957383376","data":{"timestamp":" 946957383376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957384105","data":{"timestamp":" 946957384105"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957384511","data":{"timestamp":" 946957384510"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957384816","data":{"timestamp":" 946957384816"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957385038","data":{"timestamp":" 946957385037"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957385243","data":{"timestamp":" 946957385243"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957385570","data":{"timestamp":" 946957385569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957385806","data":{"timestamp":" 946957385806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957388975","data":{"timestamp":" 946957388975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957389392","data":{"timestamp":" 946957389391"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957391917","data":{"timestamp":" 946957391917"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957392130","data":{"timestamp":" 946957392129"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957392342","data":{"timestamp":" 946957392341"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957395746","data":{"timestamp":" 946957395746"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957399422","data":{"timestamp":" 946957399422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957400458","data":{"timestamp":" 946957400457"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957403135","data":{"timestamp":" 946957403135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957403508","data":{"timestamp":" 946957403508"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957403991","data":{"timestamp":" 946957403991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957404334","data":{"timestamp":" 946957404334"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957404737","data":{"timestamp":" 946957404737"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957405212","data":{"timestamp":" 946957405211"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957405436","data":{"timestamp":" 946957405436"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957408615","data":{"timestamp":" 946957408615"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957408651","data":{"timestamp":" 946957408650"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957409380","data":{"timestamp":" 946957409379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957409784","data":{"timestamp":" 946957409783"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957410090","data":{"timestamp":" 946957410089"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957410307","data":{"timestamp":" 946957410306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957410513","data":{"timestamp":" 946957410513"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957410842","data":{"timestamp":" 946957410841"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957411081","data":{"timestamp":" 946957411079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957413666","data":{"timestamp":" 946957413665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946957413786","data":{"timestamp":" 946957413786"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_062648"," gameId":" 1331184d-574b-4cd6-b63c-f3ee2cc3e2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}